textpk.com 2014-08-29

# Privacy Policy - TextPK.com - Send free sms to any network in pakistan

|  |  |   
---  
   
| Privacy Policy  
---  
|    
---  
  
We Respect your privacy, information about you and your groups, contacts will not be disclosed to any third party unless required for legal process, we will also use your information to send you SMS about promotions occasionally

Before using our website to send free sms please don't forget to read our [Use Policy](http://www.textpk.com/use_policy.html) because we take seriously the violation of [fair use policy](http://www.textpk.com/use_policy.html)  

**Cookies** A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Our site don't use cookies. However, Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)  

**What information do we collect?**   
We collect & store every instance of your activities that are involved with TextPK.com. 

**What do we use your information for?**   
Any of the information we collect from you may be in the following ways;   
• To personalize your experience.   
• To improve app/website features based upon your interactions.   
• To send you (and/or your contacts) periodic promotions, updates and advertisements.   
• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other feature. 

**How do we protect your information**   
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information & data.   
Information about you and your conversations are never be disclosed to any third party unless required for legal process. 

**Your Consent!**   
You consent to the Privacy Policy.   

Upon registration with us you blindly agree with Privacy Policy

Privacy policy may change without prior notice.  

|   
---  

Latest Updates

Now you can receive incoming messages on your mobile.  
If you are from USA, Canada, UK and you want to receive incoming messages on your mobile, please contact us. Users from other countries may inquire too. Sender will be charged as local SMS rate.

Now you can receive SMS while you are offline!  
Great News! now whenever your friends will reply your SMS you will get an email alert too and SMS will stay in your inbox. No matter you're online or offline. Enjoy!
